Middleton, John E. Papers and IWO Publications 6406
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
John E. Middleton Papers and IWO Publications
1938-1957
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
International Workers Order
Middleton, John E.
6406
1.33 cubic feet
1.3 linear ft.
Papers, publications.
9134843
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, August 11, 2015
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 24, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
9134843
- Dissolution of the IWO, 1950-1957 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- John Middleton's Separation From the IWO, 1951-1957 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- IWO Insurance Policies on John Middleton's Family, 1939-1951 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Photographs (Box 1, Folder 4)
- IWO News Bulletin, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- The New Order, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- News From International Workers Order, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Fraternal Outlook, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Fraternal Outlook, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Fraternal Outlook, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Fraternal Outlook, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Fraternal Outlook, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Fraternal Outlook, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Fraternal Outlook, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Fraternal Outlook, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Fraternal Outlook, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Fraternal Outlook, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 5)